BOHDAN FOROSTIANYI

bohdanforostianyi@gmail.com 👩 GitHub +48 509 568 665 in LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Last-year Master's Computer Science student at AGH University Of Science and Technology in Cracow, Poland with industrial experience in software development and research and management skills obtained while leading a student research organization at the university. See LinkedIn profile for details.

SKILLS

Languages: SQL, Python, TypeScript, JavaScript, C#,

Libraries: DS & AI: PyTorch, Pandas, Numpy, SciPy,

Flask, Gradio, Google OR-Tools, Weights & Biases, **DevOps**: Docker, Kubernetes,

Frontend: Angular, React, D3.js.

PROJECTS

Python Introduction to Artificial Intelligence

repository

A software suite to assist in teaching Artificial Intelligence course at AGH University of Science and

Technology

Python, TensorFlow Probability

Lungs Lesion Detection

repository

Research project focused on detection of cancer lesions in lungs using Bayesian Neural Networks

Google OR Tools, C#

Capacity Planning Solver

repository

Solver with multiple models for fleet structure optimization problem

ReactJS, TypeScript, Julia

Schedule.it

frontend repository, backend repository

Web application for solving Nurse Scheduling Problems tailored to comply with Polish Law regu-

lations developed for charitable foundation operating in Poland.

EDUCATION

9/2018 - 1/2018 tuition waiver for the 1st vear scholarship holder for the 2nd year

Bachelor of Computer Science Full-time studies at the Faculty of Electrical Engineering, Automatics, Computer Science and Biomedical Engineering

Overall study mark: 4.61/5. Thesis: Fleet Structure Optimization in Vehicle Routing Problems.

7/2023

Machine Learning Summer School on Applications in Science ML in PL Summer School

One week Summer School providing lectures on applications of ML in math, physics, astronomy

and medicine

1/2022 - 7/2024

ongoing

Master of Computer Science

Full-time studies at the Faculty of Computer Science

Thesis: Development of Multi-Agent system for cooperation in real-time strategy environment

9/2023 - 2/2024

Exchange studies as an Erasmus student

École nationale supérieure d'informatique et de mathématiques

appliquées de Grenoble

Exchange at Data Science and Al track in Master of Science in Informatics at Grenoble programme

EXPERIENCE

10/2019 - 8/2021

Software Developer at the Rocket Team

AGH Space Systems student organization

Development of ground station for rocket hardware management

Python / Work in multidisciplinary team

7/2020 - 1/2022

Full Stack Web Developer

Comarch S.A.

· Development and support of sales management application at the Research and Development division

SQL / C# / Angular

8/2021 - 10/2023

Al Engineer

Optidata Sp. z. o.o.

· Participation in the internal research project with geospatial data analysis as primary responsibility

Development, support, testing and result verification for VRP solvers used in the company.

SQL / C# / Python / Research skills

8/2020 - ongoing

Organization leader at Glider student organization

Glider student organization

Organization of events, conference travels, members recruitment and classes

Development of educational and applied software, research

TypeScript / Python / Management skills / Research skills

LANGUAGES